Guide to the Duke University Progress Pictures Collection, 1925-1932
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- West Campus
  - 19300702WC0369.jpg (Image 539)
    - 1930-07-02
    - View showing spray pond for cooling water for ice plant in Hospital. [Dated 1930-07-01 on back of photo]
    - Hospital
  - 19300702WC0370.jpg (Image 540)
    - 1930-07-02
    - View taken from near rear of Chapel showing Chapel foundation, Auditorium and Union Building. [Dated 1930-07-01 on back of photo]
    - Chapel
  - 19300702WC0371.jpg (Image 541)
    - 1930-07-02
    - View showing front of Physics Building. [Dated 1930-07-01 on back of photo]
    - Physics
  - 19300702WC0372.jpg (Image 542)
    - 1930-07-02
    - View showing front of Group "A" Dormitory. [Dated 1930-07-01 on back of photo]
    - Craven - A
  - 19300702WC0373.jpg (Image 543)
    - 1930-07-02
    - View showing rear of Group "B" Dormitory extension. [Dated 1930-07-01 on back of photo]
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300801WC0374a.jpg (Image 544)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing the rear of Group "B" Dormitories and Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300801WC0374b.jpg (Image 545)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing the rear of Group "B" Dormitories and Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300801WC0375.jpg (Image 546)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing location of tennis courts.
    - Stadium
    - view looking towards east gate at right?
  - 19300801WC0376.jpg (Image 547)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing arcade between Group "C" Dormitories and Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300801WC0377.jpg (Image 548)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing the tower at Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300801WC0378.jpg (Image 549)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from Quadrangle near Group "B" Dormitory looking toward Medical School.
    - Campus View
    - from residential quad toward medical school
  - 19300801WC0379.jpg (Image 550)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from near Physics Building showing Chemistry Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300801WC0380.jpg (Image 551)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from near Library showing Physics Building.
    - Physics
  - 19300801WC0381.jpg (Image 552)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from Law Building showing Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19300801WC0382.jpg (Image 553)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from Group "A" Dormitory, showing North end of main Quadrangle.
    - Academic
    - view of academic quad
  - 19300801WC0383.jpg (Image 554)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing court in Group "C" Dormitories.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300801WC0384.jpg (Image 555)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from School of Religion showing foundation and first floor of Chapel.
    - Kilgo - C
  - 19300801WC0385.jpg (Image 556)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View showing Quadrangle in front of the Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19300801WC0386a.jpg (Image 557)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from Medical School tower, showing main Quadrangle.
    - Campus View
    - View of academic quad toward residential
  - 19300801WC0386b.jpg (Image 558)
    - 1930-08-01
    - View taken from Medical School tower, showing main Quadrangle.
    - Campus View
    - View of academic quad toward residential
  - 19300901WC0399.jpg (Image 559)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View taken from Medical School tower, showing top of Chemistry Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300901WC0400.jpg (Image 560)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing front of Chemistry Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300901WC0401.jpg (Image 561)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing front of Chemistry Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300901WC0402.jpg (Image 562)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing front of Law Building.
    - Law
  - 19300901WC0403.jpg (Image 563)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing rear of Auditorium stage and Union Building.
    - Residential
  - 19300901WC0404.jpg (Image 564)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing service road to the rear of Group "A" and "B" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300901WC0405.jpg (Image 565)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing rear of Group "C" Dormitories next to Union Building.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300901WC0406.jpg (Image 566)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing new tennis courts under construction.
    - Campus View
    - tennis
  - 19300901WC0407.jpg (Image 567)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing court at the rear of the Union Building, and side of Auditorium.
    - Page
  - 19300901WC0408.jpg (Image 568)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing front of Medical School and front of Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Medicine
  - 19300901WC0409.jpg (Image 569)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View taken from tower of Chapel, looking to the rear.
    - Chapel
  - 19300901WC0410.jpg (Image 570)
    - 1930-09-01
    - Picture taken from near School of Religion, showing front of Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19300901WC0411.jpg (Image 571)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View showing rear of Chemistry Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300901WC0412.jpg (Image 572)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View taken from top of terrace, looking toward Group "B" Dormitory tower.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300901WC0413.jpg (Image 573)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View taken from Group "B" Dormitory tower, looking North along main Quadrangle.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300901WC0414.jpg (Image 574)
    - 1930-09-01
    - View taken from front of Medical School, looking south along main Quadrangle.
    - Academic
    - View of academic quad
  - 19310206WC0415.jpg (Image 575)
    - 1931-02-06
    - View taken from rear of Chapel, looking toward front of same.
    - Chapel
  - 19310206WC0416.jpg (Image 576)
    - 1931-02-06
    - View taken from near center of Chapel showing top of arch windows in Memorial Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19310206WC0417.jpg (Image 577)
    - 1931-02-06
    - View showing columns in the crypt under the Memorial Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19310206WC0418.jpg (Image 578)
    - 1931-02-06
    - View taken from tower of Union Building, showing Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19310206WC0419.jpg (Image 579)
    - 1931-02-06
    - View taken from tower or Library, showing front of Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19310206WC0420.jpg (Image 580)
    - 1931-02-09
    - View taken from rear of the Botany Building, showing location of greenhouses. [Dated 1931-02-06 on back of photo]
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19310417WC0421.jpg (Image 581)
    - 1931-04-17
    - View showing interior of Chapel. Large window in the rear of Choir.
    - Chapel
  - 19310417WC0422.jpg (Image 582)
    - 1931-04-17
    - View showing details of interior of Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19310417WC0423.jpg (Image 583)
    - 1931-04-17
    - View showing details of limestone - interior of Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19310417WC0424.jpg (Image 584)
    - 1931-04-17
    - View showing front of the Chapel, taken from Administration Building.
    - Chapel
  - 19310417WC0425.jpg (Image 585)
    - 1931-04-17
    - View showing exterior of Chapel, taken from Library tower.
    - Chapel
  - 19310513WC0426.jpg (Image 586)
    - 1931-05-13
    - View showing greenhouses being erected at Duke University.
    - Botany/Zoology
    - greenhouses
  - 19311010WC0427.jpg (Image 587)
    - 1931-10-10
    - View taken from Nurses Home looking toward Hospital, showing steam and water mains for supplying Nurses Home.
    - Hospital
    - Nurses' home
  - 19311010WC0428.jpg (Image 588)
    - 1931-10-10
    - View taken from the North looking south, showing first floor of Nurses Home.
    - Hospital
    - Nurses' home
  - 19311010WC0429.jpg (Image 589)
    - 1931-10-10
    - View taken from the East looking West showing first floor of Nurses Home.
    - Hospital
    - Nurses' home
  - 19320226WC0430.jpg (Image 590)
    - 1932-02-26
    - View showing front of Nurses Home.
    - Hospital
    - Nurses' home
  - 19320226WC0431.jpg (Image 591)
    - 1932-02-26
    - View showing front of Nurses Home, taken from end nearest Hospital.
    - Hospital
    - Nurses' home
  - 19320226WC0432.jpg (Image 592)
    - 1932-02-26
    - View showing side of Nurses Home next to Hospital.
    - Hospital
    - Nurses' home
  - 19320226WC0433.jpg (Image 593)
    - 1932-02-26
    - View showing main entrance to University with Chapel in the center of picture.
    - Campus View
    - Chapel from causeway
  - 19320317WC0434.jpg (Image 594)
    - 1932-03-17
    - View showing baseball field, Duke University
    - Campus View
    - baseball field
  - 19320406WC0435.jpg (Image 595)
    - 1932-04-06
    - Picture showing front of console for the Aeolian Organ, Duke Chapel. Picture taken before console set in place.
    - Chapel
  - 19320408WC0436.jpg (Image 596)
    - 1932-04-08
    - Quarry
    - Quarry
  - 19320408WC0437.jpg (Image 597)
    - 1932-04-08
    - Quarry
    - Quarry